A Guide to the Norfolk (Va.) Building Inspection Office Architectural Drawings and Plans, 1898-1980
Library of Virginia
- [Bathroom Addition] - Permit Number: 24684, Address: 1255, 1257, 1259, 1261 Reservoir Ave., 1970, Media: Graphite on paper; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-458 (Box 35, Folder 458)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: E. F. Hardee
- [Oakwood Church of God in Christ] - Permit Number: 20400, Address: 7350 Elm St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-4 (Box 35, Folder 459)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Oakwood Church of God in Christ
- Zayre Shopping Center Addition - Permit Number: 24224, Address: 1730, 1733, 1734 E. Little Creek Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 14; Tag Number: 1970-387 (Box 35, Folder 460)
  Drawn by: Brundage, Cohen, Kroskin and Associates, Architects and Land Planners, 400 Building Street, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Barr Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Zayre, Inc.
- Temporary Shop Building for Doyle and Russell - Permit Number: 20630, Address: S/S Painter St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-51 (Box 35, Folder 461)
  Drawn by: Gresham Metal Buildings Co., Inc., ARMCO Building Systems and Products, 1060 W. 26th St., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Doyle and Russell; Commissioned by: DePaul Hospital
- Prefabricated Building for Honda of Norfolk - Permit Number: 22831, Address: 6955 Tidewater Dr., 1970, Media: Diazo prints, Thermofax; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-246 (Box 35, Folder 462)
  Drawn by: Parker Industries, Inc., Virginia Beach, VA; Chares H. Thayer, Jr., Consulting Engineer, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Glaubke Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Tidewater Motors, Inc.
- Proposed New Boiler House for J. H. Miles and Co., Inc. - Permit Number: 22596, Address: W/S Southampton Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-219 (Box 35, Folder 463)
  Drawn by: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc.; Contractor: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: J. H. Miles and Co., Inc.
- Universal Life Insurance Co. - Permit Number: 22860, Address: 2804 Virginia Beach Blvd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 13; Tag Number: 1970-249 (Box 35, Folder 464)
  Drawn by: John S. Chase, A.I.A., Architect, Houston, TX; Contractor: Lewis M. Warren; Commissioned by: Universal Life Insurance Co.
- Toback Shop - Permit Number: 26004, Address: TJ-7A Military Circle, 1971, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-117 (Box 35, Folder 465)
  Drawn by: Dudley, Morrisette, Cederquist and Associates, A.I.A., Architects and Planners, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Glenn L. Sawyer; Commissioned by: Toback Shop
- Alterations to the Texaco Building for the Virginia National Bank - Permit Number: 20452, Address: 3300 E. Princess Anne Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-14 (Box 35, Folder 466)
  Drawn by: Williams and Tazewell, Architects, A.I.A., 710 W. 21st St., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: W. A. Hall and Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: Virginia National Bank
- Proposed New Office and Shop Facilities for R. L. Harris, Inc. - Permit Number: 20543, Address: 3335 Croft St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1970-39 (Box 35, Folder 467)
  Drawn by:; Contractor: R. L. Harris, Inc., General Contractors; Commissioned by: R. H. Harris Mechanical Contractors
- Diamond Club [Alterations to Heating and Air-conditioning] - Permit Number: 22764, Address: Northampton Blvd. and Lake Wright, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-242 (Box 35, Folder 468)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Home Modernization; Commissioned by: City of Norfolk
- P and R Automotive - Permit Number: 24358, Address: 5767 Poplar Hall Dr., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-402 (Box 35, Folder 469)
  Drawn by: Cardinal Building Corp., 3653 Lenoir Circle, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Cardinal Building Corp.; Commissioned by: P and R Automotive
- [Addition] Division of Motor Vehicles, Norfolk, VA - Permit Number: 23764, Address: 5536 Iowa Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-347 (Box 35, Folder 470)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: W. H. Belanga; Commissioned by: W. H. Belanga and Associates, Inc.
- Office and Warehouse for Phillips Glass Company, Inc. - Permit Number: 20446, Address: 430 W. 24th St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-12 (Box 35, Folder 471)
  Drawn by: DeLoatch Company, General Contractors, 2917 Turnpike Rd., Portsmouth, VA; Contractor: DeLoatch Co.; Commissioned by: Jerry Logaros
- Phase III Alterations and Additions to the Virginian Pilot Ledger Star Headquarters Building - Permit Number: 24607, Address: 150 W. Brambleton Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 40; Tag Number: 1970-447 (Box 35, Folder 472)
  Drawn by: Williams and Tazewell, Architects, A.I.A., 710 W. 21 St., Norfolk, VA; Fraioli, Blum, Yesselman Assoc., Consulting Engrs.; Vansant and Gusler, Consulting Engrs.; Contractor: W. B. Meredith, II, Inc.; Commissioned by: Landmark Communications, Inc.
- Proposed Office and Warehouse Facilities for R. W. Hudgins and Son - Permit Number: 24710, Address: 307 Campostella Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-465 (Box 36, Folder 473)
  Drawn by: General Contractors, Ltd., Virginia Beach, Va.; Contractor: General Contractors, Ltd.; Commissioned by: R. W. Hudgins and Son
- [Store Alterations for] Cole National Corp. - Permit Number: 22611, Address: H-3 Military Circle, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-262A (Box 36, Folder 474)
  Drawn by: Crown Store Equipment Co., 2925 South St., Toledo, OH; Commissioned by: Cole National Corp.
- Pinedale Apartments, Leicester Avenue, Norfolk, Virginia, for Walker Realty Company - Permit Number: 24457, 24458, 24459, Address: 9019 Chesapeake Blvd.; 649 and 711 Leicester Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 10; Tag Number: 1970-409 (Box 36, Folder 475)
  Drawn by: BCHK Architects, 4100 Building, Granby St., Norfolk, Va.; Commissioned by: W. F. Thornton, Jr.
- Law Office, Frederick T. Stant, Jr., Virginia National Bank, 12th Floor - Permit Number: 22715, Address: 315 E. Main St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-234 (Box 36, Folder 476)
- 16 One Bedroom Apartment Building - Permit Number: 24714, Address: 7819 Galveston Blvd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-467 (Box 36, Folder 477)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: T. H. Nicholson, Jr.; Commissioned by: Harold McGee
- [Apartment Building] - Permit Number: 22605, Address: 9620 Grove Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo print, Electrostatic print; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1970-220 (Box 36, Folder 478)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: W. T. Thornton, Jr.; Commissioned by: W. T. Thornton, Jr.
- Three Pump Single [Gasoline Station] Island [and Sign] - Permit Number: 22691, 22692, Address: 930 Briarhill Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1970-230 (Box 36, Folder 479)
  Drawn by: Tenneco Oil Company, Engineering Dept., Houston, TX; Commissioned by: Harrell and Harrell, Inc.
- Alterations and Additions, First Presbyterian Church - Permit Number: 22709, Address: 820 Colonial Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 31; Tag Number: 1970-233 (Box 36, Folder 480)
  Drawn by: A. Hensel, A.I.A., Philadelphia, PA; Oliver and Smith, A.I.A., Norfolk, Va., Associated Architects; Contractor: Conrad Bros. Inc.; Commissioned by: First Presbyterian Church
- [Fence Surrounding Ocean View Amusement Park] - Permit Number: 20472, Address: 2-86 W. Ocean View Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1970-18 (Box 36, Folder 481)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Champion Fences, Inc.; Commissioned by: Ocean View Enterprises; Notes: Sheet shows labeled footprints of amusement park buildings and public areas circa 1960.
- Greyhound Post House [Snack Bar] - Permit Number: 24685, Address: 701 Monticello Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1970-459 (Box 36, Folder 482)
  Drawn by: Greyhound Food Management, 2301 W. Lafayette Blvd., Detroit, MI; Commissioned by: Greyhound Food Management
- Alterations to the Texaco Building for the Virginia National Bank - Permit Number: 22721, Address: 3300 E. Princess Anne Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 10; Tag Number: 1970-236 (Box 36, Folder 483)
  Drawn by: Williams and Tazewell, Architects, A.I.A., 710 W. 21st St., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: Meredith Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Virginia National Bank
- Military Circle, Norfolk, Virginia, Butler Shoes, Store No. F 3 - Permit Number: 20486, Address: 3 Military Circle, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1970-23 (Box 36, Folder 484)
  Drawn by: Toombs, Amisano and Wells, Architects, 48 Cain St. N.E., Atlanta, GA; Contractor: Robert R. Marquis, Inc.; Commissioned by: Butler Shoes
- D. P. Paul Jewelers, Military Circle - Permit Number: 20531, Address: TH-1 Military Circle, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1970-38 (Box 36, Folder 485)
  Drawn by: Bernard H. Lepselter, P. E., Consulting Engineers, 410 E. 62nd St., New York, NY; Contractor: L. J. Hoy, Inc.; Commissioned by: Gordon's Jewelers
- Military Circle, Norfolk, Virginia, Sanfred's, Store F -11 - Permit Number: 20443, Address: F 11 Military Circle, 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 12; Tag Number: 1970-10 (Box 36, Folder 486)
  Drawn by: Toombs, Amisano and Wells, Architects, 48 Cain St. N.E., Atlanta, GA; Contractor: Barr Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Military Square, Inc.
- [Alterations to Store] - Permit Number: 24557, Address: 3200 Lafayette Blvd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1970-429 (Box 37, Folder 487)
  Drawn by: Chesapeake Steel, Inc., 3468 Westminster Ave., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Powell and McClellan; Commissioned by: W. S. Allen
- New Bank and Office Building for Bank of Virginia - Permit Number: 24508, Address: 500 E. Plume St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1970-418 (Box 37, Folder 488)
  Drawn by: Spigel, Carter, Zinkl, Herman, Architects, A.I.A., 500 Plume East, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Daniel Construction Co. of Virginia; Commissioned by: Bank of Virginia
- [8 Family Apartment Building] - Permit Number: 24651, Address: 9551 27th Bay St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-453 (Box 37, Folder 489)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: W. Brunes; Commissioned by: Robert Coppage
- [8 Family Apartment Building] - Permit Number: 24359, Address: 2917 Pleasant Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-403 (Box 37, Folder 490)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: E. N. Jasper; Commissioned by: A. B. Sieloff
- [Alterations to Texaco Service Station] - Permit Number: 24216, Address: 1401 Military Hwy., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-384 (Box 37, Folder 491)
  Drawn by: Texaco, Inc., Domestic Sales Dept., Norfolk Sales Division; Contractor: Beamon Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Texaco, Inc.
- Mini-Mart [and Service Station] - Permit Number: None, Address: 6630 N. Military Hwy., 1976, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 12; Tag Number: None (Box 37, Folder 492)
  Drawn by: Murphy Oil Corp., Construction Section, Murby Building, El Dorado, AR
- [Humble Oil Signs] - Permit Number: 24728, 24729, Address: 800 Boush St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1970-469 (Box 37, Folder 493)
  Drawn by: Humble Oil and Refining Co., Marketing Dept., Operations and Engineering, Houston, Tx; Contractor: A. C. Clark Co.; Commissioned by: Humble Oil and Refining Co.
- 44 Efficiency Units Building - Permit Number: 24713, Address: 932 E. Ocean View Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 20; Tag Number: 1970-466 (Box 37, Folder 494)
  Drawn by: Brundage, Cohen, Kroskin and Associates, Architects and Land Planners, 400 Building Street, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: T. H. Nicholson, Jr.; Commissioned by: Twin Sail Corp.
- Kelton Apartments VIII - Permit Number: 24527, Address: 9519 21st Bay St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-420 (Box 37, Folder 495)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: T and K Construction Corp.; Commissioned by: T and K Construction Corp.
- [Apartment Buildings] - Permit Number: 24597, 24598, 24599, Address: 9609 24th Bay St.; 9626 and 9630 23rd Bay St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 9; Tag Number: 1970-434 (Box 37, Folder 496)
  Drawn by: Vernon A. Moore, Architect; George W. Harris; Contractor: E. N. Jasper
- [Alterations to Texaco Service Station] - Permit Number: 24214, Address: 6581 Tidewater Dr., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-382 (Box 37, Folder 497)
  Drawn by: Texaco, Inc., Domestic Sales Dept., Norfolk Sales Division; Commissioned by: Texaco, Inc.
- [8 Family Apartment Building] - Permit Number: 24543, Address: 4852 E. Princess Anne Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-422 (Box 37, Folder 498)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Keatley-Lapage Rea.; Commissioned by: Keatley
- [8 Family Apartment Building] - Permit Number: 24550, Address: 9524 25th Bay St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-427 (Box 37, Folder 499)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: E. N. Jasper; Commissioned by: Tom Powell
- Renovations and Repairs, Chesterfield Heights Elementary School - Permit Number: 24731, Address: 2915 Westminster Ave., 1970, Media: Blueprints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1970-470 (Box 37, Folder 500)
  Drawn by: Wilson B. Dodson, II, A.I.A., Architect, 716 W. 20th St., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: H. L. Tempe, Inc.; Commissioned by: City of Norfolk
- Proposed Addition Norfolk Packing Co. - Permit Number: 24153, Address: 620 E. Olney Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-372 (Box 37, Folder 501)
  Drawn by: Edwin B. Small, Architect-Engineer, 1904 Lafayette Blvd., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: C. C. Foreman and Son, Inc.; Commissioned by: Norfolk Packing Co.
- "Pegasus" Service Station, 3 Bay-Front Enter- L. H. - Permit Number: 24227, Address: 247 E. Little Creek Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 11; Tag Number: 1970-388 (Box 37, Folder 502)
  Drawn by: Mobil Oil Corp., Service Station Engineering Dept., New York, NY; Commissioned by: Mobil Oil Corp.
- [Alterations to Texaco Service Station] - Permit Number: 24212, Address: 3857 E. Little Creek Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-380 (Box 37, Folder 503)
  Drawn by: Texaco, Inc., Domestic Sales Dept., Norfolk Sales Division; Contractor: Diversified Contractors, Inc.; Commissioned by: Texaco, Inc.
- Alfriend and Canoles Law Offices, Virginia National Bank - Permit Number: 24345, Address: 315 E. Main St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-399 (Box 37, Folder 504)
- Apartment Building for Mr. Willard Bunn - Permit Number: 24269, Address: 2531 E. Ocean View Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1970-394 (Box 37, Folder 505)
  Drawn by: Vernon A. Moore, Architect, 1217 Hazel Ave., Chesapeake, Va.; Contractor: Willard H. Bunn; Commissioned by: Willard H. Bunn
- McLea School Porch Revision - Permit Number: 24366, Address: 745 Bancker Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1970-405 (Box 37, Folder 506)
  Drawn by: Arthur Konikoff, Architect, 9 Tidewater Executive Center, Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Target Construction; Commissioned by: Ruth Ingram (McLea School)
- 12 Unit Apartment Building - Permit Number: 24553, Address: 9621 8th Bay St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-428 (Box 37, Folder 507)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Stuart A. Drummond
- [Signs for First Virginia Bank] - Permit Number: 24369, 24370, Address: 230 W. York St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1970-406 (Box 37, Folder 508)
  Drawn by: Federal Sign and Signal Corporation; Contractor: Talley Neon; Commissioned by: First Virginia Bank
- Proposed Interior Changes to Building Located at 509 Botetourt St. - Permit Number: 24267, Address: 509 Botetourt St., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-393 (Box 38, Folder 509)
  Drawn by: Edward R. Lacy, II; Contractor: O. S. Jarnell; Commissioned by: John Manos
- Dover Court Apartments - Permit Number: 24347, Address: 863, 865 Bancker Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1970-400 (Box 38, Folder 510)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Gray Development and Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Gray Development and Construction Corp.
- 32 Single Bedroom Apartments - Permit Number: 24232, Address: 1433-1445 Kingston Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 6; Tag Number: 1970-389 (Box 38, Folder 511)
  Drawn by: Vernon A. Moore, Architect, Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: Clarence H. Byler; Commissioned by: Condos Corp.
- Alterations and Additions to American Legion Post 204 - Permit Number: 24202, Address: 3514 Cheshire Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints, electrostatic print; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-379 (Box 38, Folder 512)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: American Legion- Dalton and Cartier Post 204
- [2 Signs for Virginia National Bank] - Permit Number: 24313, 24314, Address: 3300 Princess Anne Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-396 (Box 38, Folder 513)
  Drawn by: Colite Industries, Inc., 228 W. Parson St., West Columbia, SC; Contractor: Talley Neon; Commissioned by: Virginia National Bank
- Norview Gardens Apartments for Fine and Salzberg, Inc. - Permit Number: 24465, 24466, 24467, 24468, Address: 7109-7117, 7123-7131, 7113-7135 Sewells Point Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 9; Tag Number: 1970-411 (Box 38, Folder 514)
  Drawn by: Washington Associates, Architects and Engineers, Norfolk, VA; Commissioned by: Fine and Salzberg, Inc.
- [Alterations to Texaco Service Station] - Permit Number: 24215, Address: 1511 Little Creek Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-383 (Box 38, Folder 515)
- Ford Motor Company [Dealership Signs] - Permit Number: 24625, Address: 7520 N. Military Hwy., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-449 (Box 38, Folder 516)
  Drawn by: Plasti-Line, Co., Knoxville, Tn.; Contractor: Talley Neon; Commissioned by: Bruce Flournoy Motor Co.
- [Alterations to Texaco Serivce Station] - Permit Number: 24213, Address: 8346 Tidewater Dr., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-381 (Box 38, Folder 517)
- [Alterations to Texaco Service Station] - Permit Number: 24218, Address: 7480 Tidewater Dr., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-386 (Box 38, Folder 518)
- BPOE Norfolk Lodge # 38 Storage Room Addition - Permit Number: 24256, Address: 1231 Typo St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-390 (Box 38, Folder 519)
  Drawn by: Alfred Ellis Abiouness; Commissioned by: Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks Lodge #38
- 6 or 8 One Bedroom Units for Keatley-LePage Realty - Permit Number: 25191, Address: 4858 E. Princess Anne Rd., 1971, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 4; Tag Number: 1971-48 (Box 38, Folder 520)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: J. D. Keatley and George A. LePage
- Remodel Existing House - Permit Number: 24380, Address: 6249 Virginia Beach Blvd., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1970-407 (Box 38, Folder 521)
  Drawn by: BCHK Architects, 4100 Building, Granby St., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: J. W. Creech, Inc.; Commissioned by: Roughton Pontiac Corp.
- Colonial Conversion # 1 for "EM" Type Building [Texaco Service Station Alterations] - Permit Number: 24217, Address: 7601 Granby St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-385 (Box 38, Folder 522)
- Proposed Alterations to Wards Corner Office of First Virginia Bank of Tidewater - Permit Number: 24681, Address: 143 E. Little Creek Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-456 (Box 38, Folder 523)
  Drawn by:; Contractor: L. J. Hoy, Inc.; Commissioned by: First Virginia Bank of Tidewater
- Proposed Alterations to Existing Building for Mr. Israel Steingold - Permit Number: 24682, Address: 1169 Military Hwy., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-457 (Box 38, Folder 524)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Israel Steingold
- Shop Building Addition - Permit Number: 24545, Address: 3460 Strathmore Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-424 (Box 38, Folder 525)
  Drawn by: Chesapeake Steel, Inc., 3468 Westminster Ave., Norfolk, VA; Contractor: Chesapeake Steel, Inc.; Commissioned by: Chesapeake Steel, Inc.
- Addition to Virginia Shee [Metal] - Permit Number: 24149, Address: 3322 Chesapeake Blvd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-371 (Box 38, Folder 526)
  Drawn by: Norfolk Iron and Wire Works, Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: Norfolk Iron and Wire Works, Inc.; Commissioned by: Virginia Sheet Metal
- Burger Chef Systems, Inc., Modernation - Permit Number: 24180, Address: 208 E. Little Creek Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 1; Tag Number: 1970-376 (Box 38, Folder 527)
  Drawn by: Burger Chef Systems, Inc.; Contractor: Barr Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Burger Chef, Inc.
- Massachusetts Mutual Life Insurance Company, Virginia National Bank Building- 16th Floor - Permit Number: 24344, Address: 315 E. Main St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 3; Tag Number: 1970-398 (Box 38, Folder 528)
- R. E. Michel Co., Inc. - Permit Number: 24329, Address: 2610 Arkansas Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-397 (Box 38, Folder 529)
  Drawn by: Commercial Building Services, Inc.; Contractor: Commercial Building Services, Inc.; Commissioned by: R. E. Michel Co., Inc.
- Additions and Alterations to King's Daughters Hospital - Permit Number: 24705, 24706, Address: 601 Colley Ave., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 12; Tag Number: 1970-464 (Box 38, Folder 530)
  Drawn by: Williams and Tazewell, Architects, A.I.A., 710 W. 21st St., Norfolk, Va.; Contractor: E. T. Gresham Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: King's Daughters Hospital
- [Pool for] George M. Kaufman - Permit Number: 24691, Address: 1045 North Shore Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo print; Sheets: 2; Tag Number: 1970-460 (Box 38, Folder 531)
  Drawn by: Master Pools by Schertle, 9916 Jefferson Ave., Newport News, VA; Contractor: Master Pools by Schertle; Commissioned by: G. M. Kaufman
- Dover Court Apartments - Permit Number: 24348, Address: 867 Bancker Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 7; Tag Number: 1970-401 (Box 38, Folder 532)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Gray Development and Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Gray Development Corp.
- [Signs for] International House of Pancakes - Permit Number: 24146, 24147, Address: 1153 N. Military Hwy. and 200 Blk. E. Little Creek Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 19; Tag Number: 1970-370 (Box 39, Folder 533)
  Drawn by: Plasti-Line, Co., Knoxville, Tn.; Contractor: Cardinal Sign Corp.; Commissioned by: International House of Pancakes
- 8 Unit Apartment Building - Permit Number: 24189, Address: 428 Staten St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1970-378 (Box 39, Folder 534)
  Drawn by: Washington Associates, Architects and Engineers, Norfolk, VA; Commissioned by: D. C. Harris
- Dover Court Apartments - Permit Number: 24264, Address: 857, 859, 861 Bancker St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 5; Tag Number: 1970-391 (Box 39, Folder 535)
  Drawn by: Unsigned; Commissioned by: Gray Development Co.
- Temporary Penthouse for Bell Telephone Building - Permit Number: 23071, Address: 120 W. Bute St., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 15; Tag Number: 1970-274 (Box 39, Folder 536)
  Drawn by: Lee, King, and Poole, Architects, Southern States Building, Richmond, VA; Contractor: Basic Construction Co.; Commissioned by: Bell Telephone Co.
- Remodeling of Existing Service Station - Permit Number: 23182, 23183, Address: 1542 E. Little Creek Rd., 1970, Media: Diazo prints; Sheets: 8; Tag Number: 1970-281 (Box 39, Folder 537)
  Drawn by: Scot Stations, 817 Connecticut Ave. NW, Rm 117, Washington, DC; Commissioned by: Petroleum Marketing Corp.